<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>work &#8211; Scott Kosman.</title>
	<atom:link href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/category/work/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/</link>
	<description>Est. 1976. Technical Director and possible Fictional Character.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 17:12:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.11</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Think Just Play</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/dont-think-just-play/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=58</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;d been asked by the beautiful people at Fronteers to present a 10-minute talk at their &#8220;Jam Session,&#8221; which takes place the evening before their annual web development conference. Rather than present yet another technical-oriented talk as all of the other presenters would be doing, I decided to take a different tactic and actually present&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/dont-think-just-play/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;d been asked by the beautiful people at <a href="http://fronteers.nl/">Fronteers</a> to present a 10-minute talk at their &#8220;Jam Session,&#8221; which takes place the evening before their annual web development conference. Rather than present yet another technical-oriented talk as all of the other presenters would be doing, I decided to take a different tactic and actually present on public speaking. My thinking was that in this industry, everyone is going to have to present something at some point, whether to a small group of colleagues, as a pitch to a prospective client, or speaking at an industry gathering. Drawing on my experience as a former church preacher (seriously!) I gave a lightning talk on some key tactics to make yourself a better public speaker. As fate would have it, I was chosen to give the opening talk of the night, which of course led to me referring to myself as the Fronteers keynote speaker. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/2.2.1/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>The talks were all recorded, so below is a video of me presenting as well as my slide deck from the presentation.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/51827394" width="848" height="477" frameborder="0" title="Scott Kosman | Don&#039;t Think, Just Play | Fronteers 2012 Jam Session" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="699" id="talk_frame_6800" mozallowfullscreen="true" src="//speakerdeck.com/player/506caf672d77290002019afe" style="border:0; padding:0; margin:0; background:transparent;" webkitallowfullscreen="true" width="848"></iframe>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>jQuery Performance Article for 24Ways.org</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/your-jquery-now-with-67-less-suck/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=56</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[http://24ways.org/2011/your-jquery-now-with-less-suck In late 2011 I had the incredible opportunity to write an article on jQuery performance techniques for 24ways.org, &#8220;the advent calendar for web geeks.&#8221; This was a great experience for me as a technical writer (something I hadn&#8217;t done much of up until now) and the positive feedback I recieved was overwhelming. I don&#8217;t&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/your-jquery-now-with-67-less-suck/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://24ways.org/2011/your-jquery-now-with-less-suck">http://24ways.org/2011/your-jquery-now-with-less-suck</a></p>
<p>In late 2011 I had the incredible opportunity to write an article on jQuery performance techniques for 24ways.org, &#8220;the advent calendar for web geeks.&#8221; This was a great experience for me as a technical writer (something I hadn&#8217;t done much of up until now) and the positive feedback I recieved was overwhelming. I don&#8217;t have exact stats on the article, but it&#8217;s one of the most highly-commented on articles 24ways have posted, and there&#8217;s some GREAT discussion in the comments, too.</p>
<p>24ways have been doing their thing for seven years now, and it&#8217;s more than a little bit humbling to see myself listed on the Authors page along with luminaries of the industry like Jeffrey Zeldman and Eric Meyer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ready 4 What&#8217;s Next</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/ready-4-whats-next/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=52</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The challenge was to build an holistic social media campaign that brought the playfulness of Rubik’s Cube, the fun of personalisation, and the technology of 3D interactivity to mobile, desktop and social touch points. As a topper, we had to bring the social media campaign to life in real events across North America where visitors&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/ready-4-whats-next/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The challenge was to build an holistic social media campaign that brought the playfulness of Rubik’s Cube, the fun of personalisation, and the technology of 3D interactivity to mobile, desktop and social touch points. As a topper, we had to bring the social media campaign to life in real events across North America where visitors could seamlessly integrate their real-world experience with that of the social and digital campaign.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/77177289" width="848" height="477" frameborder="0" title="Toyota Rav4 - Case Film" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Supported by the installation and flash banners, users can play with a Rubik’s Cube on their Facebook timeline, then customise their own and share that across Twitter and Facebook.</p>
<p><a href="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/RAV4_bts_06.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-103" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/RAV4_bts_06.jpg" alt="RAV4_bts_06" width="935" height="526" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/RAV4_bts_06.jpg 935w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/RAV4_bts_06-300x169.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/RAV4_bts_06-400x225.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 935px) 100vw, 935px" /></a></p>
<p>We managed the process through a carefully planned and well-documented process of Conceptual Development, Tech R&amp;D, UX Design, Visual Design and Development to bring together this campaign that allows users to access the 3D gameplay across all modern desktop browsers and mobile devices.</p>
<p><em>Note: this project isn&#8217;t currently available online since the campaign ended, I&#8217;m working on bringing a static version back up. <a href="http://prayingmadness.com/contact/">Feel free to let me know</a> if you want to be notified when that happens! –S.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kaspersky Cybermap</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/kaspersky-cybermap/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=50</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[http://cyberwar.kaspersky.com/ With access to a wealth of real time data, we created an interactive WebGL experience that dramatically brings to life every detection made by Kaspersky software, happening at that very moment, around the world.We denoted different threats with colours and geometric symbols. Some show the point of detection while others show the source of&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/kaspersky-cybermap/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://cyberwar.kaspersky.com/">http://cyberwar.kaspersky.com/</a></p>
<p>With access to a wealth of real time data, we created an interactive WebGL experience that dramatically brings to life every detection made by Kaspersky software, happening at that very moment, around the world.We denoted different threats with colours and geometric symbols. Some show the point of detection while others show the source of the threat as well, with bright, arcing trajectories linking source to destination. Users can zoom in and out of either a globe or flat map view to pinpoint the major threats and identify the most infected areas. A breakdown of each country’s level of infection can be triggered with a click, along with the ability to directly select your own country and share statistics through social. <img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-76" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_02.jpg" alt="kap_02" width="1300" height="790" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_02.jpg 1300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_02-300x182.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_02-1024x622.jpg 1024w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_02-400x243.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1300px) 100vw, 1300px" /></p>
<p>The visualization went on to feature on big screens at Kasperksy Lab events and trade shows around the world, using a specially designed demo mode which takes the audience on an autopilot fly-through that descends down to ground level and right into the heat of the action. The combination of true data and live statistics with an engaging user experience, tells a compelling story and hopefully provides Kaspersky with an eye-catching way to raise brand awareness, showcase their products and possibly remind a few people of their favorite childhood 80’s movies!</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-77" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_03.jpg" alt="kap_03" width="1300" height="790" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_03.jpg 1300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_03-300x182.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_03-1024x622.jpg 1024w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/kap_03-400x243.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1300px) 100vw, 1300px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>22tracks</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/22tracks/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=48</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It’s not everyday you get to work on a product you really love. It’s even more rare that you get a chance to redesign it. But that’s basically what happened when we were approached by 22tracks to design and develop an alternative to their hugely popular music curation website. http://22tracks.mvtest.net [opens/ in new window] VICE Media&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/22tracks/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>It’s not everyday you get to work on a product you really love. It’s even more rare that you get a chance to redesign it. But that’s basically what happened when we were approached by 22tracks to design and develop an alternative to their hugely popular music curation website.</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://22tracks.mvtest.net/" target="_blank">http://22tracks.mvtest.net/</a><em> [opens in new window]</em></p>
<p>VICE Media and UM orchestrated a collaboration between 22tracks and IE -part of bigger campaign- to imagine a version of their site that was optimized for IE11′s impressive new feature set, especially the WebGL support and multi-touch support. We were brought in right at the beginning to look at the core qualities of both website and browser and reassess 22tracks.com based on our findings. There followed an intense design phase where we looked at how we could really optimize the user experience for touch while preserving the simplicity and function of the existing 22tracks website. And all this within a fully responsive HTML5 framework that would adapt to multiple devices. We organized the playlist browsing and track-related functionality into two opposing drawers that allow users to perform multiple contextual interactions while keeping the music pumping.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-80" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_01.jpg" alt="22t_01" width="935" height="526" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_01.jpg 935w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_01-300x169.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_01-400x225.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 935px) 100vw, 935px" /></p>
<p>The center-piece (literally), is a dial device that contains the usual track controls but also a 360 degree way to tap through the 22 tracks of each playlist and also an outer circle which allows users to scrub through each track by swiping around a dynamic equalizer-type graphic. While we finessed the intricacies of the UI we also began concepting an audio-visualiser that would accompany the music. We wanted this to be graphically minimal – taking cues from the existing 22tracks look and feel – and really and truly responsive to the music. We also wanted it to be interactive, partly to showcase the multi-touch capabilities of IE11.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-81" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_02.jpg" alt="22t_02" width="935" height="526" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_02.jpg 935w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_02-300x169.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/22t_02-400x225.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 935px) 100vw, 935px" /></p>
<p>We decided on a direction we called ‘Blobs’. Amorphous distorted circles spawn from the center of the player and then float off around the screen, pulsing and moving to different aspects of the music. Different blobs react to different frequencies, certain types react in different ways to others and they are all effected by gravity and the tilt of the device’s accelerometer. Users can grow new blobs from their finger tips, pinch, stretch and pluck existing blobs as well as inflating them to bursting point (whereupon they explode into 22 ‘blobdules’ (see what we did there?) – all without missing a beat. Ultimately this was a significant design and technology challenge. This kind of experience is not normally something that happens in browsers, let alone multiple browsers on multiple devices. And it’s got blobs in it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Channel 4 News Wall</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/channel-4-news-wall/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=46</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[http://4newswall.com/ In an effort to reach a younger target demographic, UK television network Channel 4 decided to turn to the one media format that all of the kids are using these days. Animated .gifs. Yep. We built this site on Tumblr, but in the process of doing so hacked Tumblr like it was attacking my&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/channel-4-news-wall/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://4newswall.com/">http://4newswall.com/</a></p>
<p>In an effort to reach a younger target demographic, UK television network Channel 4 decided to turn to the one media format that all of the kids are using these days.</p>
<p>Animated .gifs.</p>
<p>Yep.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-105 size-full" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/4newswall.gif" alt="4newswall" width="200" height="200" /></p>
<p>We built this site on Tumblr, but in the process of doing so hacked Tumblr like it was attacking my family. Pushing Tumblr in directions it was never meant to go has become somewhat of a hobby as of late and in the end it turned out to be a near-perfect CMS for this sort of thing. The benefit of pushing all .gif content to followers&#8217; Tumblr Dashboards helped spread the site farther and wider than we ever hoped imaginable. A combination of Tumblr and an S3-powered Backbone application keeps everything humming nice and smoothly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Karenina Live</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/karenina-live/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 12:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=40</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[http://karenina.withgoogle.com/ Google Russia wanted to demonstrate that it does more than simply understand local culture – it actively contributes to it. So we dreamt up a project that took one of the most cherished Russian literary masterpieces of all time and reintroduced it to a modern audience using Google technology. Together with Google we created&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/karenina-live/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://karenina.withgoogle.com/">http://karenina.withgoogle.com/</a></p>
<p>Google Russia wanted to demonstrate that it does more than simply understand local culture – it actively contributes to it. So we dreamt up a project that took one of the most cherished Russian literary masterpieces of all time and reintroduced it to a modern audience using Google technology.</p>
<p>Together with Google we created a brand new edition of Leo Tolstoy’s masterpiece “Anna Karenina” using Google’s exclusive Hangout technology. An online version, narrated live from front cover to back cover by the Russian people.</p>
<p>More than 700 people from all over the world read Leo Tolstoy’s novel on-line on the Internet for 36 hours in a row…</p>
<p>It was an extraordinary event – a relay-race of storytelling, that unified the most disparate people through one extraordinary story: from the Russian President’s Press Secretary to opposition bloggers; from TV stars in Moscow to everyday workers in Russia’s remotest regions.</p>
<p>Here are some results:</p>
<ul>
<li>Unprecedented PR Coverage in Russia – 5.4b of impressions (900+ articles in online and offline media, 55 radio spots and 78 TV spots). 6 prime time newsblocks about the project on the biggest Russian channel &#8211; First Channel, that covers 90% of population in Russia.</li>
<li>6M views of promo video</li>
<li>3M playbacks of livestream</li>
<li>20 000 followers and 4 mln impressions on Google+ page</li>
<li>4x surge in “Karenina” search queries during 2-day livestream</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Self-Destructing Book</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/self-destructing-book/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 11:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=19</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[http://selfdestructingbook.com/ For the launch of James Patterson’s new book Private Vegas, we took the inherent thrill of this novel to a spectacular, new height. We created the Self-Destructing Book. An integrated campaign designed to bring to life the most thrilling reading experiences ever. We gave people 24 hours to read “Private Vegas” before it self-destructed.&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/self-destructing-book/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://selfdestructingbook.com/">http://selfdestructingbook.com/</a></p>
<p>For the launch of James Patterson’s new book <em>Private Vegas</em>, we took the inherent thrill of this novel to a spectacular, new height.</p>
<p>We created the Self-Destructing Book. An integrated campaign designed to bring to life the most thrilling reading experiences ever. We gave people 24 hours to read “Private Vegas” before it self-destructed.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/118767422" width="848" height="477" frameborder="0" title="The Self-Destructing Book - Case Study" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>1,000 fans had 24 hours to read an advance digital version of the book until it self­-destructed in a spectacular fashion. Thousand of others followed along and interacted with the readers. Unique codes were created and released in batches throughout the 5 days of the experience.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-26 size-full" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_02.jpg" alt="sdb_02" width="1085" height="649" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_02.jpg 1085w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_02-300x179.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_02-1024x613.jpg 1024w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_02-400x239.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1085px) 100vw, 1085px" /></p>
<p>Readers and online users were connected, and to increase the adrenaline in their race against the clock, people visiting the site were able to “sabotage” the readers’ timers and steal time from them.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-25 size-full" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_01.jpg" alt="sdb_01" width="1085" height="709" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_01.jpg 1085w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_01-300x196.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_01-1024x669.jpg 1024w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_01-400x261.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1085px) 100vw, 1085px" /></p>
<p>The iPad-only reading experience included a menacing page burner that destroyed every page as the user swiped it. To intensify the thrill, a control panel informed readers when someone stole time from them and when other books were destroyed.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-27 size-full" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_04.jpg" alt="sdb_04" width="1085" height="562" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_04.jpg 1085w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_04-300x155.jpg 300w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_04-1024x530.jpg 1024w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/sdb_04-400x207.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1085px) 100vw, 1085px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soma FM Now Playing</title>
		<link>https://prayingmadness.github.io/soma-fm-now-playing/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 10:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[scott kosman]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://prayingmadness.com/?p=60</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Any time I&#8217;m in a position to have to learn a new technology platform, my &#8220;Hello, world&#8221; of choice is to build a fairly simple Now Playing widget for SomaFM internet radio – basically allowing a user to instantly see what track is playing on any of their stations at any given time. In the last couple&#8230; <p class="more-link-p"><a class="more-link" href="https://prayingmadness.github.io/soma-fm-now-playing/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Any time I&#8217;m in a position to have to learn a new technology platform, my &#8220;Hello, world&#8221; of choice is to build a fairly simple Now Playing widget for <a href="http://somafm.com/">SomaFM</a> internet radio – basically allowing a user to instantly see what track is playing on any of their stations at any given time.</p>
<p>In the last couple of years I&#8217;ve done this twice: in 2013 for Panic&#8217;s <a href="https://panic.com/statusboard/">Status Board</a> iPad app and most recently for the <a href="https://getpebble.com/">Pebble Smartwatch</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/soma_statusboard.png"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-116" src="http://prayingmadness.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/soma_statusboard.png" alt="soma_statusboard" width="275" height="274" srcset="https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/soma_statusboard.png 275w, https://prayingmadness.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/soma_statusboard-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 275px) 100vw, 275px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>Wanna have a play?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>If you&#8217;re a Status Board user you can add the widget to your own iPad by <a href="panicboard://?url=http%3A%2F%2Fsomafm.prayingmadness.com&amp;panel=diy">tapping here</a>.</li>
<li>If you have a Pebble, <a href="http://apps.getpebble.com/en_US/application/55a7f76374e429d266000040">oh hey look over here</a>.</li>
</ul>
<p>And if you have neither device handy but still want to peek under the hood, both codebases are on Github: <a href="https://github.com/humantorch/Soma-FM-panel-for-Status-Board">Status Board</a> | <a href="https://github.com/humantorch/pebble-somafm">Pebble</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
